Qasim Ali Zahid

Senior Software Engineer

Experienced Ruby on Rails Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Ruby on Rails, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, , C++, Python, and SQL. Strong engineering professional, graduated from the University Of Sargodha, Sargodha.



Pakistan

github.com/qasimali-tx

+92-3035570992

S qasimali@techcreatix.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer Healthwire

11/2022 - Present Lahore

Healthwire is on a mission to use technology to empower patients and improve healthcare outcomes.

Team Lead

Techcreatix

12/2021 - 11/2022

Senior RoR Developer

Southville Solutions

07/2021 - 12/2021 Lahore

RoR Developer

Techcreatix

06/2019 - 07/2021 Lahore

EDUCATION

BSCS

University of Sargodha, Sargodah

02/2015 - 05/2019

ICS(Physics)

Govt. College Ravi Road Lahore

04/2013 - 01/2015

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Healthwire (11/2022 - Present)

 Pharmacy, Hospital Management System, Practice Management System, Health-records, Online Store for Medicine.

RL-Node (01/2022 - Present)

 Inventory Management system to track out total usage of medicine at different points.

ShipOracle (07/2021 - 12/2022)

 Search engine type application based on Ruby on Rails with Chat, Feeds, Mails Notifications

Abacus (07/2021 - 11/2022)

 Web-based portal (with RoR Backend programming) for Payments and Reports

QuickCard (03/2019 - Present)

 A blockchain based POS with checkouts. ledgers to maintain transactions data and generate reports.

A1 Covid Testing (01/2022 - Present)

 Web-based portal (with RoR back-end programming) for healthcare and offering a range of highly accurate tests for coronavirus detection.

LANGUAGES



